Guide to the Arthur A. Allen papers,1899-1968,
Allen, Arthur A. papers,1899-1968,
- Series XI. Phonographic Records and Sound Recordings
  - Tape Recordings
    - Western Birds - Sides 3 and 4, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9939 (Box 158)
    - Western Birds - Sides 5 and 6, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9940 (Box 158)
    - "Birds in Your Garden" - Sides 1 and 2, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9941 (Box 158)
    - "Dawn in the Duck Blind", undated; 1/4" reel TR-9942 (Box 159)
    - Trumpeter Swan, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9943 (Box 159)
    - Whooping Crane and Sandhill Crane, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9944 (Box 159)
    - Whooping Crane, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9945 (Box 159)
    - European Meadowlark, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9946 (Box 159)
    - Wood Cock, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9947 (Box 159)
    - "Off the Wing Tip", undated; 1/4" reel TR-9948 (Box 159)
    - Labrador birds, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9949 (Box 159)
    - "Birds in Your Garden" - Side 1, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9950 (Box 159)
    - "Introduction to Lab", undated; 1/4" reel TR-9951 (Box 159)
    - Mr. David Burpee - Myna bird call, 1957; 1/4" reel TR-9952-9953 (Box 159)
    - Unidentified bird recording, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9995-TR-9996 (Box 160)
    - Song Sparrow, Pheasant, Robin, Grouse (possibly Parrot), undated; 1/4" reel TR-9997 (Box 160)
    - From Arthur Allen's window: May 24- July 1, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9998 (Box 160)
      Canada Geese; Starling; Grackled; Woodducks
    - In Arthur Allen's Office: July 1, undated; 1/4" reel TR-9999 (Box 160)
      Grackles; Swan; Mallards; Woodducks; Robin; blackbirds
    - Material for Dr. Allen, undated; 1/4" reel TR-10000 (Box 160)
      Orchard Orioles; Catbird